■
字幕來源：影視帝國
後期：筆信·Lee    Sung1219
大巧局
Family Plot
有人在這裡
Someone is here.
不太靠近
Not closely.
不太情願
Not willingly.
我感到了阻礙
I feel a holding back.
有什麼麻煩  亨利
What's the trouble, Henry?
太多回憶  太多痛苦
Too many memories, too much pain.
太多悲傷
Too... much... sorrow.
無論和你在一起的是誰
Whoever is there with you,
讓他們說話  亨利
tell them to speak up, Henry.
讓他們靠近一點
Tell them to come closer.
我想我知道那是誰  布蘭琪夫人
I think I know who it is, Madame Blanche.
我想我知道是什麼困擾著她
I think I know what's bothering her.
"她"是嗎  別擔心  蘭伯特女士
Her, is it? Never you mind, Miss Rainbird.
沒有你的指示  亨利不會做任何事的
I won't have you doing Henry's work for him.
現在  讓我們一起來吧  親愛的
Now, let's have it, my love.
這就是為什麼今晚我們在這裡
That's why we're here tonight.
為了幫助我的朋友  擺脫她的痛苦
To help my friend be rid of her torment.
她有休息的權力  讓她疲憊的頭腦
She has a right to rest her weary head
能在枕頭上歇息  於每個晚上
on a pillow each night...
平靜地安睡  有如天使
and sleep the peaceful sleep of the angels.
你怎麼知道我有睡眠的困擾
How did you know about my troubled sleep?
誰告訴你的
Who told you?
她夜晚無法長睡
Her nights cannot go on like this much longer.
我從來沒有告訴別人我的噩夢
I never told a soul about my nightmares.
-你怎麼會  -是誰來到這裡
- How could you...  - Who is this person who arrives...
今晚我們的存在  所以才不敢靠近嗎
in our presence tonight, but does not dare to come close to us?
是她  是我的妹妹哈麗葉
It's her. It's my sister Harriet.
-絕對是  -她保持距離
- It must be.  - She stays her distance,
朱莉亞·蘭伯特  因為她沒有感受到
Julia Rainbird, for she does not feel...
你的愛或是你的善意
your love or your kindness yet.
你太自私了
There is selfishness where you are.
我已經什麼都為她做了
I've had all I can take from her.
她每晚都來到我的夢中
Night after night, coming into my dreams.
發牢騷  抱怨  努力使我感到內疚
Whining, complaining, trying to make me feel guilty,
就好像我需要她來告訴我是非
as though I need her to tell me right from wrong.
告訴她  我知道該怎麼做
Tell her I know what has to be done.
我一直想這麼做已經一年了
I've been wanting to do it for a year.
但是我  朱莉亞·蘭伯特  已經做出決定了
But it is I, Julia Rainbird, who has made the decision.
我不需要她來鞭策我
I don't need her to goad me on!
他們在我夢中醜陋的話語  使我生病
They're making me ill with their ugly words in my ugly dreams.
告訴她該停止了  回去  不要管我
Tell her to stop it, to go away and leave me alone.
喔  不  不  別讓她走
Oh, no. No, no. Don't let her go!
-別讓她離開  -哈麗葉
- Don't let her go away.  - Harriet?
哈麗葉  留下來  哈麗葉
Harriet, stay with us, Harriet.
你姐姐要和你說話
Your sister wants to speak to you now,
從她的心靈深處
from the depths of her soul.
怎麼了  怎麼回事
What's wrong? What is it?
她說"我已經等了好久"
She says, "I've waited so long...
"想聽到你說話  朱莉亞"
"to hear from you, Julia.
"沒有你在  我很不快樂"
I've been so unhappy without you."
是你  哈麗葉
It is you, Harriet.
喔  我很抱歉
Oh, I'm so sorry!
我不該讓你那麼做的
I-I should never have made you do it.
喔  都已經過去了
Oh, it's all past now.
但是我會盡我所能地去彌補
But I'll do what I can to make up for it.
如果他還活著  我會找到你的兒子
If he's still alive, I'll find your son.
我會帶他到我身邊並且愛他
And I'll take him in my arms and love him...
有如我就是你  我可憐的哈利葉
as if I were you, my poor Harriet.
我會  我會待他如己出
And I'll... I'll make him one of us.
給予他一切  一切
And give him everything. Everything!
離太遠了
Far away.
離太遠  太遠了
So far, far away.
但  但我需要她的協助
Bu-But I need her. I need her help.
我一個人做不到
I can't do it alone.
你看  我需要她的記憶
You see, I need her memory.
那都已經40年了  我不知道孩子被帶到哪裡
It's over 40 years ago, and I don't know where the child was taken...
或是送給了誰
or who it was given to.
我不知道他現在在哪裡  或他現在是誰
I don't know where he is now or who he is.
對於衡量朱莉亞·蘭伯特  真實的愛
The true measure of Julia Rainbird's love...
在於她現在要如何去做
lies in what she does now,
藉由你的幫助  當然  還有我的
with your help, of course, and mine,
親愛的  離開吧
and that of the dear, departed one...
是誰漂流遠離了我們
who has drifted so far from us.
我們瞭解了  蘭伯特女士  對吧
We understand him. Don't we, Miss Rainbird?
噢  是的  我是  我願意去做任何事  任何的事
Oh, yes. Yes, I do. I'm willing to do anything. Anything at all.
最後  幸福將會到來
In the end, there will be happiness.
從逝去的眼淚當中  沙漠般的心靈會開出花朵
From the tears of the past, the desert of the heart will bloom.
再見  朱莉亞·蘭伯特  再見  布蘭琪
Good-bye, Julia Rainbird! Good-bye, Blanche.
再見
Good-bye.
布蘭琪夫人  你沒事吧
Madame Blanche! Are you all right?
噢  這是
Oh. It was...
這到底是怎麼回事
What in the world's been going on here?
我覺得我好像做了什麼事
I feel as though I've been properly done over.
你不記得發生什麼了
Don't you remember what happened? Mm-mm.
不記得細節了  布蘭琪女士  只有大略
Not the details, Miss Rainbird, only the gist,
你應該知道我的意思
if you know what I mean.
我以為你會告訴我一些要點
Suppose you give me the gist of it.
喔  我不知道
Oh well, I wonder...
我能麻煩你弄點什麼喝的
Could I trouble you for a sip of something? Ju-Just...
噢  當然  你要喝什麼
Oh, of course. What would you like?
噢  隨便給我一點混合的
Oh, a double shot of anyth...
-來點雪莉酒或許比較好  -噢  是的  沒問題
- A spot of that sherry might be nice.  - Oh, yes. Of course.
謝謝
Thank you.
-現在  請告訴我還記得的招魂內容  -說個大概
- Now, tell me what you remember of the seance.  - In a nutshell?
拜託了
Please.
嗯
Well...
大約40年前  你安排
About 40 years ago, you arranged to have...
把你妹妹的小嬰兒送給了別人
your sister Harriet's baby given away without a trace.
如今你總是做噩夢  你困惑的良心告訴你
And now your bad dreams and troubled conscience tell you...
必須去找到長大了的小孩  並帶他回家
to find the grown-up person, take him into the family...
給予他財富
and bestow your wealth on him.
-很好  -謝謝
- Excellent.  - Thank you.
但我為什麼  要強迫我妹妹把小孩送人
And why did I force my sister to give the child away?
我想  那個小孩可能是  私生子  蘭伯特女士
I guess the kid was a... illegitimate, Miss Rainbird.
我不希望你以為我是個清教徒  布蘭琪夫人
I don't want you to think me a puritan, Madame Blanche.
但是  40年前  未婚母親
But 40 years ago, an unmarried mother...
並不像現在這麼普遍
was not the commonplace it is nowadays.
尤其是在我們這樣的家族
And in a family like ours,
不得不犧牲一切代價來掩蓋醜聞
a scandal had to be covered up at all costs.
我明白
I understand.
我必須保持傳統
And I'm still sufficiently old-fashioned,
並維護蘭伯特家的名聲
and sufficiently protective of the Rainbird name,
尋找失蹤的繼承人時
to want to seek the missing heir...
必須以私人並秘密的方式進行
in a private and secret fashion,
而不是去找偵探社
rather than go to detective agencies...
或是登報尋人
and put notices in the newspapers.
這是個明智的決定  蘭伯特女士
A most wise decision, Miss Rainbird.
那麼  現在  我們找到了必須請你幫忙的理由
Well, now, suppose we get to the reason...for my sending for you.
我已經78歲了
I'm 78 years of age.
我希望能帶著一顆平靜的心  跨進棺材
I would like to go to my grave with a quiet conscience.
特別是當我知道唯一的繼承人  就在外面的某個地方
Particularly as I know that my only heir is out there somewhere,
是我的行為  剝奪了他蘭伯特的姓氏
deprived by my acts of his true Rainbird name.
你能用你的力量幫助我嗎
Will you help me with your powers?
如果你是誠心的  我可以
If in your heart you believe that I can,
我有責任讓我們共同去嘗試  蘭伯特女士
then I owe it to both of us to try, Miss Rainbird.
不  我太老了  做不到了
No, I'm too old for trying.
我只來得及去看到結果
I've only time enough left for results!
幫我找到他  布蘭琪夫人
Find him for me, Madame Blanche.
用你的精神力量  還有你的亨利
Use your spirit-control, your "Henry."g
透過我的妹妹
Get through to my sister.
找到她的兒子  查出他是誰  無論他的身份
Find her son, whoever he is, wherever he is,
我會付給你一萬美元
and I'll pay you $10,000.
一萬
Te...
如果你是真心的  蘭伯特女士
Only if you genuinely wish to, Miss Rainbird.
但是不要認為這些錢是付給了我
But let's not think of this as a payment to me.
因為我很有愛心
There are many causes dear to my heart,
世上所有的慈善機構都需要它
which need all the charity the world can spare.
你不知道它讓一個女人多麼振奮  我的財富
You've no idea how refreshing it is for a woman of my wealth...
找個人只需要用到這麼一點點錢
to find someone who has so little use for money.
謝謝
Thank you.
那麼  我想我們已經談妥了
Well, now, I regard our arrangement as completed.
我的睡覺時間到了
I... It's my bedtime.
我必須向你這位  令人愉快的客人告別了
I must take leave of your delightful company.
對我來說這是一個難忘的夜晚  蘭伯特女士
This has been a most memorable evening for me, Miss Rainbird.
你讓錢發揮了更大的價值
See to it that you make it a rewarding one.
你讓自己反覆的陷入險境
At the risk of repeating myself,
我希望你不要忘記
I hope you will not forget...
沒有人  絕對沒有任何人  能知道我們的尋找行動
that nobody, absolutely no one, should know of our search.
蘭伯特家的名聲必須受到保護
The Rainbird name must be protected.
我保證守口如瓶
My jaw is locked.
一言為定  再見了  感謝你的光臨
On that note, I will say good-bye, and thank you for coming.
事情怎麼樣了
So, how'd it go?
我不知道  扮演亨利  簡直是在謀殺我的喉嚨
I don't know. Having to do Henry is murder on my throat.
-謀殺  -是  是  我明白
- Murder.  - Yeah, yeah. I know.
-那事情怎麼樣了  -她上鉤了  就等著被拉上來
- So how did it go?  - She's hooked, waiting to be pulled in.
另一條價值25元的沙丁魚
Another one of your $25 sardines?
不  這是條大魚  喬治  一條大鯨魚
No. This is a big one, George. A great big whale.
哦  快點  告訴我
Well, come on. Give.
把你的眼睛留在路上  別催我
Keep your eyes on the road. Don't rush me.
好的  布蘭琪
Okay, Blanchie.
洗耳恭聽
Start way up at the top.
嗯  就像收聽ABC廣播一樣簡單
Well, it was as simple as A-B-C.
亨利來找我  來自天上
Henry came to me from the Upper Brightness,
低聲對我說"這位女士長期有睡眠的困擾"
whispered to me, "This womars been having sleep problems."
之後就順其自然  按照邏輯
From there on, things followed naturally, logically.
啊哈  我一次又幫了你大忙啊  親愛的
Aha! So I came through for you again, didn't I, darlin?
不  你在說什麼  喬治
No. What are you talking about, George?
你是什麼意思  我說了什麼
What do you mean, what am I talking about?
你他媽的知道我在說什麼
You know damn well what I'm talking about.
所有的資訊  是我向當地的藥劑師挖來的
All that information that I dug up by gabbir to the local druggist...
關於她被失眠搞得快發瘋
about how she was drivir him crazy...
試圖沒有處方購買安眠藥
tryir to get sleeping pills without a prescription!
這本來對我非常非常有用
That could have been very, very useful to me.
為什麼你沒告訴我這些事
Why didn't you tell me about that?
你什麼意思  我沒告訴你  你他媽的知道我告訴過你
What do you mean, why didn't I tell you? I told you. You know damn well I told you.
不  你總是以為你告訴過我事情  但其實你忘了
No, you always think you tell me things, and you forget to.
我必須跨越天堂與地獄  去和亨利溝通
I have to go through heaven and hell, the Great Beyond, with Henry.
亨利  聽好  是我
Henry, my ass. It was me.
總是我
It's always me.
如果沒有我的調查  你這通靈人不過是個干臘腸
Without my research, you're about as psychic as a dry salami.
齷齪  齷齪  齷齪
Nasty. Nasty, nasty.
我已經厭煩了當你的水晶球
I'm sick and tired of having you hang me by the crystal balls.
顧好你自己的水晶球吧  喬治
Leave your crystal balls out of this, George.
不  別談亨利了  把廢話留給你的客戶吧
No, let's leave Henry out of this and keep the bullshit for your customers.
你嫉妒他  是嗎
You're jealous of him, aren't you?
喔  拜託  布蘭琪
Oh, please, Blanche.
我喜歡你的嫉妒  這是你這駕駛的臭味
I like your jealousy. It's your driving that stinks.
嘿  聽著  我偶爾也是個演員  不是計程車司機
Hey, look. I happen to be an actor, not a cab driver.
我當然能扮演司機  但我相信地獄不需要一位駕駛
I can play cab drivers, but I sure as hell don't have to drive like one.
哦  直到我賺到  朱莉亞·蘭伯特這一票以前
Well, until I can collect from Julia Rainbird,
恐怕你需要  繼續扮演好計程車司機
I'm afraid you're gonna have to go on playing a cab driver.
我們倆都不希望餓死
Neither of us seems to be very fond of starving to death.
哦  我們該如何幹這票  這條蘭伯特鯨魚能噴出多少錢
Well, how are we supposed to collect? How much is this Rainbird whale gonna spout up?
你要繼續扮演好私家偵探
Also, you're gonna have to go on playing a private eye.
上帝  不  我已經演夠了私家偵探
Christ, no! I've had it playing private eyes.
上帝  是的  喬治
Christ, yes! Now, George.
停止褻瀆吧
Stop blaspheming.
你想要詛咒十張大鈔
You wanna put the curse on ten big ones?
等一等  布蘭琪
Now, wait a minute, Blanche.
-你說十張大鈔  -嗯哼
- Did you say ten big ones?  - Mm-hmm.
-一萬  -嗯哼
- Ten thousand?  - Mm-hmm.
-美元  -美元  喬治
- Dollars?  - Dollars, George!
現在  布蘭琪  你想想
Now, Blanche, you got any idea...
我們能如何花這一萬美元
what you and I could do with ten grand?
嗯哼  我們甚至可以結婚
Mm-hmm. We could even get married.
為什麼你總是要掃興呢
What are you always a wet blanket for?
哈  你太誇獎我了
Oh, you flatter me so.
那麼  怎麼做  我們該做什麼
Well, what's the deal? What do we have to do?
我晚點會在床上告訴你的
I'll tell you about it in bed, afterwards.
噢  拜託  布蘭琪  給我一點暗示
Aw, come on, Blanche. Give me a hint.
只是一點  前戲
Just a little... Fore play.
好吧  找一個人  就這樣
All right. Find one man. That's all.
哦  我們做過更糟糕的事  他叫什麼名字
Well, we've had to do worse than that. What's his name?
呃  沒有人知道
Hmm. Ah... nobody knows.
-那麼  他是誰  -好問題  沒有人知道
- Well, who is he?  - That's a problem. Nobody knows.
-他在哪裡  -沒有人知道
- Where is he?  - Nobody knows.
喔  別說笑了
Well, for chrissake!
你的意思是  都沒有人知道  布蘭琪
You mean, nobody knows, Blanche?
沒有人知道他的名字  他在哪裡  或者他是誰
Nobody knows his name, or where he is, or who he is?
嘿  喬治  別叫了
Well, George, stop yelling.
有個人可能會知道
There's a possibility of one person who might have known.
-哦  是誰  -朱莉亞·蘭伯特沒有對我提到他
- Well, who's that?  - Julia Rainbird didn't mention him to me.
幸運的是  她的朋友愛達·庫克森跟我說了
Fortunately, her friend Ida Cookson did.
-哦  那是誰  -蘭伯特的私人司機
- Well, who is it?  - The Rainbird family chauffeur.
哦  你總算說出了一條正道
Well, now you're talkir. Now we're on our way.
麻煩的是  呃
Trouble is... Well,
他已經死了25年
he's been dead for 25 years.
喔  別再說笑了  布蘭琪
Oh, for chrissake, Blanche...
喔  不不不  別緊張  喬治
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, don't start to fret, George,
否則今晚我們在水床上  將會失去樂趣
or our water bed will be no fun at all tonight.
做為一個演員  你應該知道  煩躁會毀了演出的
As an actor, you should know fretting will ruin a performance.
你該不會是在擔心  我今晚的表現吧
You're not gonna have to worry about my performance tonight.
事實上  今天晚上
As a matter of fact, uh, on this very evening,
你會想要起立鼓掌的
you're gonna see a standing ovation.
她在這裡  不  不是男的  是個女人
She's here. No, not a man. It's a woman.
好的  跟我來
Right. Follow me.
只要維克多·康斯坦丁  還在你手上  我們就不能動你
As long as you've got Victor Constantine, we can't touch you.
所以  你不如把那東西放下吧
So you might as well put that thing away.
你一直稱自己為"交易人"因此我們以為你是一個男人
You've been calling yourself"The Trader," so we thought you were a man.
我認為我們也應該得到一些保證  確認肉票仍然活著
I think we deserve some assurance that the victim is still alive.
按照你的指示  無線電已經從直升機上移除
All radios have been removed from the helicopter, as you instructed.
"康斯坦丁先生正在昏睡當中
"Mr. Constantine will be unconscious but in perfect condition when picked up.
只要等安眠藥藥效退去就會醒來"
Just let him sleep the drug off."
好吧  警長  開燈
All right, Sergeant, turn on the lights.
-別逞英雄  -是的  先生
- Don't try and be a hero.  - Yes, sir.
好  我們已經盡了我們的部分
Well, we've done our part.
我們要去哪
Where are we going?
別發生任何該死的錯誤
Not one goddamn mistake.
還要飛多遠
How far are we going?
你運氣真好  他們還願意為肉票付出
It's lucky for you they've still got the victim.
更重要的是我把你扔下去  這件事沒發生在你身上
I'd like nothing better than to toss you right out of this thing on your head.
當然  這趟小旅行是你預訂的  不是嗎
You sure have this little trip mapped out, don't you?
我打賭  那東西甚至沒裝子彈
I bet that thing isn't even loaded.
高爾夫球場
Golf course, huh?
耀眼  非常完美
Brilliant. Absolutely perfect.
我的腳快斷了  這該死的六英吋高跟鞋
My feet are killing me. These damn six-inch heels.
我恰巧喜歡高挑的女人
I happen to like tall women.
每個人都喜歡高挑的女人
Everybody likes tall women.
事實上  每個人都在尋找  高挑的女人
In fact, everyone's going to be looking for a tall woman.
但總是不盡如人意
Aside from complaining a lot,
你最近都在做些什麼
what have you been doing with yourself lately?
噢  沒什麼  抱贖金啦  諸如此類的事情
Oh, nothing much. Picking up a ransom, that sort of thing.
你有看到任何  我們不知道的人嗎
Did you see anyone, uh, we know?
有兩個看來是警察  另外第三個絕對是FBI
Two men who look like police and a third who just had to be F.B.I.
最常和你打交道的人
You mix with the nicest people.
家常便飯
Beats housework.
-你有對他們說什麼  -一個聲音也沒發出
- Did you say anything to them?  - Not a syllable.
你看吧  親愛的
Now, you see, honey?
我說過你可以學著緘默  只要你去嘗試
I told you you could learn to keep your mouth shut, if you tried.
瞧瞧是誰在這裡
Look who's here.
嗯  有沒有人看到一位身材高挑的
Mm. Has anyone seen a tall,
金髮美女  剛才她還在這裡
blonde woman around here lately?
喔  走掉了  有誰會需要她
Gone, poof! Who needs her?
我要  至少多留點時間給我吧
I do. At least one more time.
好了  親愛的
Let me put that there, darlin.
康斯坦丁先生給我們  留了一點葡萄酒
Mr. Constantine has left us some wine.
我不認為他喜歡進口的東西
I don't think he likes the imported stuff.
嗯  還有我的牛肉乾酪
Uh... It was probably my veal parmesan.
我想我煮得太爛了
- I'm afraid I overcooked it.
他喜歡在餐廳吃東西  就這樣
- He likes eating in a room with a view, that's all.
你知道  有錢人很挑剔的
You know how fussy rich people are.
別忘了洗乾淨
Don't forget to empty that out.
你不覺得洗馬桶  有損寶石收藏家的尊嚴嗎
Don't you think emptying a chemical toilet... is below the dignity of a jewel collector?
-真是罪惡的工作啊  亞瑟  -我明天再做
- The wages of sin, Arthur.  - I'll do it tomorrow.
不能拖到明天
Never put off till tomorrow...
-或是你今晚也可以先略過  -婊子
- what you can empty out tonight.  - Bitch.
亞瑟  阿姆斯特丹是怎樣的地方
Arthur, what's Amsterdam like?
喔  大量的運河
Oh, lots of canals.
很多乾癟的老頭
Lots of wizened old men...
坐在大石頭上  以銳利的目光盯著年輕人
with sharp eyes, sitting around cutting big stones into little ones.
你會看到的
You'll see.
我不知道什麼是影響我  今晚我渾身感到不舒服
I don't know what's come over me tonight. I'm tingling all over.
我告訴過你危險的  不是嗎
I told you about danger, didn't I?
首先  它使你生病
First it makes you sick.
當你平安度過  它又讓你非常
Then, when you get through it, it makes you very,
非常熱愛
very loving.
-親愛的  這  -嗯
- Darling, is it...  - Hmm?
這太過容易了  讓人害怕
It was all too easy. It's frightening.
出色的計劃
Brilliant planning.
他們沒有任何線索可以追蹤
They don't have a single lead to follow.
我們對他用的麻藥有效嗎
What about the ketamine we stuck him with?
哦  如果沃格爾醫生六個月前  拔我的臼齒時有效
Well, if Doctor Vogel didn't miss it six months ago when I had my wisdom tooth out,
現在對他一樣有效吧
he's not gonna miss it now.
不要在這裡浪費時間了  我們上床吧
Don't finish up in there. Let's go to bed.
-累了嗎  -嗯  全身酸痛
- Tired?  - Mm-mm. Tingling all over.
為什麼我會讓你佔有這一切
How'd I ever let you get me into all this?
我想我愛上了你  因為我需要一些穩定
I thought I fell in love with you because I needed some stability.
哦  我猜只是你的性格不好
Well, I guess you're just a bad judge of character.
-你把到手的鑽石放在哪  -大家都看得到的地方
- Where'd you put the diamond, dear?  - Where everyone can see it.
-你才沒有  -我有
- You didn't.  - I did.
-你要告訴我在哪裡嗎  -你得先折磨我
- Are you gonna tell me where?  - You'll have to torture me first.
喔  我正打算呢
Oh! I intend to.
就在幾分鐘後
In a few minutes.
我已經夠尊重FBI和督察局了
Now, with all due respect to the F.B.I. And the Bureau of Inspectors,
我沒有時間玩遊戲
I have no time to play games.
不要忘記  先生們  我已經強烈的想離開這個辦公桌
Now, lest we forget, gentlemen, I have been away from this desk forcibly.
我還有許多工作趕著做
I've got a lot of work to catch up on.
這該死的事情  我們還要談多少回
Now, how many more times we gonna go through this goddamn thing?
直到我們找到線索為止  康斯坦丁先生
Until we come up with something, Mr. Constantine.
這種解決綁架的方法真是地獄
That's a hell of a way to solve a kidnapping.
康斯坦丁先生  你要知道
Mr. Constantine, you're not the first victim, you know.
你不是第一個受害者  還有其他人
There have been others.
好了  好了  但是從我這裡  你們也得不到線索的
All right, all right. But from me, you'll learn absolutely nothing.
-你永遠不會知道  -我知道
- You never know.  - I know.
好吧  弗伊
All right. Floyd?
現在  從地下停車場說起
Now. The underground garage.
-停滿了車  -聲音呢
- Full of cars.  - Sounds?
-有個人在我身後  -是男人還是女人
- People, behind me.  - Was it a man, or was it a woman?
-我不知道  -男人還是女人
- I don't know.  - Man or woman?
-男人  -然後呢
- Man.  - Then what?
就在我正要轉身時  我的肩膀一陣刺痛
It was a prick in my shoulder. I started to turn.
接著  我在一個房間裡醒來
Eh...And I woke up in a room.
是的  你有聽到什麼嗎  屋內或屋外的聲音
Yes, and what did you hear? Inside or outside?
房間是隔音的
The room was soundproofed.
我什麼都聽不到  除了揚聲器裡傳來空洞的聲音
I never heard anything except a disembodied voice of a loudspeaker.
-描述一下  -但我已經說過了
- Describe it.  - But I've already done that.
再說一次
Again!
是一個男人的聲音  沒有口音
It was the voice of a man, no accent.
-電子變聲過  無法辨識  -有幾個人在那裡
- Doctored up electronically. Unrecognizable.  - How many of them were there?
兩個  一男一女
Two. A man and a woman.
-你為什麼這麼說  -因為只有微弱的光線照射下來
- Why do you say that?  - Because the faintest light filtered down from above.
不足以給我機會看看他們是誰
But not enough to give me a chance to see who they were.
-那麼是誰煮飯  -她煮的
- Yes, and who did the cooking?  - She did.
-為什麼  -因為男人不會費心思
- Why?  - Because a man would not bother to put the parsley...
在魚排上放香芹  這就是原因
on the filet of sole, that's why.
-她多大年紀  -喔  拜託
- How old is she?  - Come on, now. Please.
-她多大年紀  -25
- How old is she?  - Twenty-five.
-為什麼  -為什麼
- Why?  - Why?
如果像我這樣年齡的男人  要被一個女人綁架
Because if a man my age is gonna get kidnapped by a woman,
他希望她有25歲  這就是原因
he wants her to be 25, that's why.
-描述一下你如何被釋放  -釋放
- Describe your return.  - The return.
那空洞的聲音叫我坐下來  並背對著門
The disembodied voice tells me to sit with my back to the door.
燈光熄滅  門打開  他們走了進來
The light goes out, the door opens, they both come in.
我感到左手臂一陣刺痛
I feel a prick in my left arm.
接下來我只知道  我在醫院的病床上醒來
The next thing I know, I wake up in that hospital bed...
你就坐在那裡  開始問東問西的
with you sitting there, thinking up questions!
謝謝  康斯坦丁先生  你做得很好
Thank you, Mr. Constantine. You're doing great.
-這就是你的感想  -好  讓我們重頭開始
- That's what you think.  - All right, let's start all over again.
噢  媽的
Aw, shit!
亨利  為什麼你面帶微笑
Why, Henry, you have such a beaming smile on your face.
我微笑是因為我很高興  布蘭琪
I smile because I'm happy, Blanche.
能透過你  布蘭琪  傳達訊息給你朋友  愛達·庫克森
It comes through you, Blanche, from your friend, Ida Cookson.
我是她的嚮導  亨利
I'm her guide, Henry.
只有在不被否認的時候  才能稱為真正的友誼
Friendship can be claimed only when it cannot be denied.
告訴愛達·庫克森  我們在這裡都很感謝
Tell Ida Cookson we're all thankful here...
她溫暖而寧靜的心靈
for the warm tranquility in her heart.
因為她信任你  使得這更加溫暖
It will grow even warmer as she trusts in you,
向你傾訴  沒有對你保留秘密
and confides in you, and holds back no secrets from you...
無論是對她自己  或是她的親密朋友
be they her own, or those of her intimate friends.
你聽到了嗎  庫克森夫人
Did you hear that, Mrs. Cookson?
是的  布蘭琪夫人
Yes, Madame Blanche.
亨利  我需要你  幫我們尋找沃爾特
Henry, I want you to seek Walter for us now.
透過善意的尋找  直到
Search through to the Double Strand of Kindness, until...
我的朋友愛達·庫克森  能加入這愛的交流
my friend Ida Cookson is joined in loving communication...
與她親愛的丈夫溝通
with her dear, departed husband.
我試試看  布蘭琪
I will try, Blanche.
但是首先  必須讓迷霧消散  並揭起薄紗
But first, the mist must part a little, and the veil must rise...
讓光線指引我們道路
to let in the light that will show us the path.
我準備好了  亨利
Ah, I'm ready now, Henry.
準備  準備好了跟隨你  無論你要我去哪兒
Ready! Ready to follow you, wherever you want me to go.
哪裡  你要帶我到哪裡  亨利
Where? Where are you taking me, Henry?
是的  是的  我看到了
Yes, yes, yes! I see.
我看到你在向我招手
I see your hand beckoning to me.
喔  多麼迷人的花園啊  亨利
Oh, what a lovely garden, Henry.
我  我  喔
My, my. Oh!
那是  那是一尊雕像嗎
Is that... Is that a statue there?
噢  那是沃爾特站在噴泉旁邊嗎
Oh! Could this be Walter standing beside the fountain?
-你怎麼能這樣對我  -我需要你的車鑰匙
- How can you do this to me?  - I need your car keys.
-我趕時間  -喔
- I'm in a hurry.  - Oh!
你知道打斷我的思緒  會造成什麼損害嗎
Do you realize what damage you can do my psyche, breaking in this way?
只要給我你的鑰匙  我趕時間
Just give me your keys. I need 'em.
是的  亨利  要幹嘛
Yes, Henry! What for?
我找到蘭伯特司機的女兒了
I've located the daughter of the Rainbird chauffeur.
-我這計程車司機卻去不了  -喔
- And I'm not going as a cab driver.  - Oh!
-你說我應該做的  我卻沒有車  -我才不在乎你做什麼
- What am I supposed to do without my car?  - I don't care what you do.
-我開計程車  只要給我鑰匙  -樹在搖動
- Take a taxi. Just give me the keys.  - The trees are swaying!
枝葉分開了
And the branches part!
但那兒一個人也沒有  在這裡
But there's no one there! Here.
我看到影子消失了  空氣越來越冷
I see shadows falling! The air is getting cold!
光線變暗了  再見  亨利
The brightness... dims. Good-bye, Henry!
喔
Oh!
你找到沃爾特了
Did you find Walter?
-在哪裡  -在廚房裡啊
- Where?  - In the kitchen.
沒錯
I did.
我不知道能不能和你談幾分鐘  海妮根女士
I wonder if I could speak to you for a couple minutes, Mrs. Hannagan.
當然  我們認識嗎
Why, sure. Do we know each other?
不  我叫法蘭克·麥克布萊
No, I'm Frank McBride,
弗格森和麥克布萊律師事務所的
of the law firm of Ferguson, Ferguson & McBride,
我只是想知道  如果你不介意
and I just wondered if you would mind...
回答一些關於你背景的問題
answering a couple questions about your background.
-我的背景  -嗯
- My background?  - Mm-hmm.
就像洗碗水一樣無趣
Dull as dishwater.
我的意思是  你為什麼會想知道這個
I mean, what in the world would you be wanting with that?
呃  這樣說吧  嗯
Well, let's just say that the, uh,
我對那些訊息感興趣  是因為值不少錢
information that I'm interested in could be won'th a great deal of money.
哦  是嗎  給誰
Oh, yeah? To who?
嗯  我們只要花一點點時間  問幾個愉快的小問題
Well, we'll get around to that pleasant little subject in a minute,
如果你不介意
if you don't mind.
-好吧  -太好了
- Okay.  - Oh, swell.
現在  我們從頭開始吧
Now, why don't we just start at the beginning?
-你的父母呢  -喔  他們都過世了  蒙主寵召
- Your parents.  - Oh, they're both dead. God rest 'em.
-你的父親是一名司機  對吧  -你怎麼知道
- Your father was a chauffeur, though, right?  - How did you know that?
他是蘭伯特家族的司機
He was a chauffeur for the Rainbird family.
又說對了  你像是個冥界的偵探  麥克布萊先生
Right again! You'd be a hell of a detective, Mr. McBride.
這我可就不知道了  親愛的
I don't know about that, my dear.
這段時間  你還記不記得有誰
Now, during this period of time, though, can you remember anybody, uh,
是你父親的親密朋友
being a close friend of your father's?
嗯  是有一個人  很久以前了  當時我還在讀書
Uh, there was a man. It was away back when I was in school.
那人經常和我父親一起喝啤酒
Uh, there was this guy that my father used to drink beer with...
並一起到村裡打撞球
and shoot pool with down in the village.
這哈利·休奎奇  和他太太莎蒂開了一間家禽店
This Harry Shoebridge had a poultry shop with his wife, Sadie.
休奎奇
Shoebridge.
是啊  他的生意一直很差
Yeah. His business was always lousy,
即使在景氣好的時候
even when times were good.
她曾經流產過
And she used to have miscarriages...
就像其他女人一樣不再過生日
like other women have birthdays.
後來  他們放棄並搬走了
Well, they stopped trying, and they moved away...
搬到巴洛溪去  並收養了一個小孩  我想
to Barlow Creek, and, uh, adopted a kid, I think.
-男孩嗎  -是啊  一個嬰兒
- A boy?  - Yeah. An infant.
但是  你知道的  我不太確定
But, you know, I'm not so sure.
我  記憶有些模糊  嗯
I... It's all kind of hazy, an-and, uh,
我試著回想
I keep connecting it with...
嗯  我記得有一晚
Well, I remember this night...
我父親從休奎奇那裡  一個人開車回家
with my Dad driving over there... to the Shoebridge's all alone, and then getting in...
然後和我媽媽大吵了一架  因為他回到家時已經凌晨四點了
a big fight with Ma because he'd come home at 4:00 A.M.,
且他不告訴她  他到底去做了些什麼
and he wouldn't tell her what he was doing or something.
現在  我父親過世了  願上帝保佑他的靈魂安息
Now, after my dad passed away... God rest his soul...
我媽媽非常痛恨休奎奇
my ma was damn mad at the Shoebridge's,
因為他們一直沒有來參加葬禮
because they never showed up at the funeral.
-後來  她發現了原因  -為什麼
- Then she found out why.  - Why?
就在一年前  他們參加了自己的葬禮
A year earlier, they'd gone to their own funeral.
-死了  -嗯
- Dead?  - Mm-hmm.
-他們和房子一起燒死了  -那麼  小孩怎麼了
- Their house burned down with them in it.  - Well, what about the son?
海妮根女士  你沒看到有顧客嗎
Mrs. Hannagan! Can't you see that there are customers?
-噢  好的  我馬上過去  -她馬上過去  夫人
- Oh, yes. Yes. I'll be right there.  - She'll be right there, ma'am.
嗯  聽著  麥克布萊先生
Uh-Uh, look, um, Mr. McBride,
-事情差不多就這樣了  -海妮根女士
- about all this being won'th something...  - Mrs. Hannagan!
-好的  -等一下
- Yeah.  - Wait a second.
我到哪裡才能找到  休奎奇的兒子
This Shoebridge son... where do I look for him?
嗯  到巴洛溪公墓試試吧
Well, try the Barlow Creek Cemetery.
什麼意思  到公墓
What do you mean, the cemetery?
嗯  我不確定  但我認為他死了
Well, I'm not sure, but I think he's dead, too.
抱歉
Sorry!
死胡同  布蘭琪
Dead end, Blanche.
早就埋葬了
Dead and buried.
-我是管理人  能為你做什麼嗎  -我是這家庭的朋友
- Caretaker. Do somethir for you?  - I'm a friend of the family.
什麼都沒留下  這差事糟透了
None left. Bad business, that.
你是指大火嗎
You mean the fire?
我不喜歡他們同時被埋葬
Never liked them multiple funerals.
太多工作都擠在同一時間
Too much work involved, all at one time.
他們是一起死的  但他們沒有埋在一起
They died together, yet they're not... buried together in the same hole.
為什麼
How come?
我怎麼知道
Search me.
瞧這裡
Here. Look.
1950年過世
Died in 1950. Died 1950.
Died 1950.
這兩個死亡日期相同
Both died the same date.
舊石碑
Old stone.
而這個是新的石碑
This is practically new stone.
-真是聰明人  -怎麼  被我發現什麼了
- Smart fellow, ain't ya?  - Why? Have I stumbled on to something?
哦  很高興認識你
Well, nice meetir ya.
我該回去幹活了  明天在這兒還有份工作
Better get back to my work. I got a job comir in here tomorrow.
把那該死的東西關小  瑪西洛
Turn that damn thing down, Marcella.
我甚至聽不到自己的說話聲
Can't even hear myself think.
你想我怎麼可能  記得那麼久以前的事情
How do you expect me to remember anything that far back?
我必須要翻閱我的舊檔案  來找資料才行
I'd have to go through my old files for that kind of information.
嗯  威勒先生  我不喜歡堅持
Well, Mr. Wheeler, I hate to insist...
你知道嗎  麥克布萊先生
You know something, Mr. McBride?
你們律師全都一樣
You lawyers are all alike.
麻煩  麻煩  麻煩
Trouble, trouble, trouble.
來吧  我可沒有整天的時間
Well, come on. I don't have all day.
你說的那一家是哪一年死的
What year did you say the family died?
嗯  1950年
Uh, 1950.
幾月
What month?
這我可幫不了你
Ah, I can't help you there.
-我能坐下嗎  -好  請便
- Shoebridge. Shoebri...  - Can I sit down?  - Yeah, go ahead.
休奎奇  休奎奇
Shoebridge. Shoebridge.
喔  在這兒"休奎奇  哈利和莎蒂"
Oh, here it is. "Shoebridge: Harry and Sadie.
"大型大理石  28號"
"Large marble. Model 28.
"全額支付  檢索編號93"
"Paid in full. Check number 93.
"第一教堂末世聖徒  巴洛溪"
First Church of Latter Day Saints, Barlow Creek."
那兒子呢
What about the son?
-艾迪·休奎奇  他們的兒子  -艾迪
- Edward Shoebridge. He's their son.  - Edward?
-是的  -好  不
- Yeah.  - Okay. Nope.
-沒有  -什麼意思  沒有
- Nothing.  - What do you mean, nothing?
肯定有  或許他比較晚來
There's gotta be something. Maybe it came later.
等等  你是說艾迪·休奎奇  他的墓碑
Wait a minute. You're talking about Eddie Shoebridge. His headstone?
是的  他比較晚來
Yeah, that did come later.
我想是  嗯  65號
I think in, uh, '65.
是的  我記得那孩子
Sure, I remember that kid.
他在這裡太受歡迎  有人說是他自己放的火
He wasrt too popular around here. Some say he set that fire himself...
為了擺脫他的家人然後消失
to get rid of his family, and then disappeared...
使他看起來  像是也在大火中喪生
to make it look like he died in the fire too.
他們從來沒發現他的屍體
They never did find his body.
你是說沒有屍體在他的墳墓中
You mean, there's no body in that grave?
嗯  我記得  這就是為什麼當地的牧師
Well, as I recollect, that's why the local parson...
沒有為艾迪做任何事的原因
wouldn't say any services for Eddie.
沒有死亡證明嗎
Well, Wasrt there a death certificate?
我不知道  我也不需要知道
I wouldn't know about that. And I don't need to know.
我只是個生意人  麥克布萊先生
I'm just a businessman, Mr. McBride.
啊  在這兒
Ah, here it is.
"艾迪·休奎奇  特級花崗岩"
"Edward Shoebridge. Granite special.
"11月12日訂製"
"Ordered, November 12.
"1965年11月18日支付"
"Paid for, November 18, 1965.
"395美元"
$395."
有趣的是  他以現金支付
Now, that's funny. It's paid in cash.
-他們通常不會這樣做  -那是誰
- They don't usually do that.  - Who was it?
我不知道  麥克布萊先生
I don't know, Mr. McBride.
我猜他不想讓人知道他的名字
I guess he didn't want his name known.
什麼意思"他"
Well, what do you mean, he?
-你剛才說"他"-我有說嗎
- You just said he.  - I did, didn't I?
哦  你知道的  我依稀記得好像  是個男人
Well, you know, I seem to sort of remember... that it was a man.
對了  年輕小伙子
Yeah. A young fella.
微禿  我猜他20多歲
Slightly bald. I'd say in his late twenties.
你有沒有再見到他  嗯  安置墓碑的時候
And did you see him again when you, uh... Put in the headstone?
我們並沒有這樣做  是他自己來把墓碑帶走的
We didn't do that. He came by and picked it up himself.
對  我想起來了  用一輛拖車
Yes, I remember now. In one of those tow trucks.
-你知道  那種拖車庫的  -我知道
- You know, the kind that garages use?  - Gotcha.
不  這裡沒有  艾迪·休奎奇的死亡證明
No, there is no death certificate here for Edward Shoebridge,
只有哈利·休奎奇和  莎蒂·休奎奇的
only Harry J. Shoebridge and Sadie L. Shoebridge.
就只有這樣
That's all you have?
哦  這裡還有
Well, there is this.
似乎曾有人為艾迪·休奎奇  申請死亡證明書
It appears to be an application for a death certificate...
日期是1965年11月4日
for one Edward Shoebridge, dated November 4, 1965.
"由於申請人無提供任何死亡證據"
"Inasmuch as applicant could furnish no proof of death...
"當事人的屍體一直未被尋獲"
"for party whose body had never been found,
"沒有提供醫療死亡證明書"
"and who could supply no medical death certificate,
"亦沒有法醫檢驗  該申請被拒絕"
"and nothing from the coroner's office, the application was denied.
"申請人接獲通知後可到法院訴訟"
"Applicant, when informed he could file a petition for court action,
"但拒絕了這項建議"
declined the suggestion."
有說申請人是誰嗎
Does it say who the applicant was?
有"申請人喬森·馬洛尼"
Yes. "Request was made by Joseph P. Maloney,
"巴洛溪426大街"
426 Main Street, Barlow Creek."
-很好  謝謝你  -不客氣
- Attagirl. Thank you.  - You're welcome.
-加滿  -麻煩你
- Fill 'er up?  - Please.
-你要檢查引擎嗎  -如果你可以  麻煩你
- You want to check under the hood?  - If you would, please.
-小心火柴  -喔  好的
- Better be careful with those matches.  - Oh. Right.
抱歉
Sorry.
-這店是你開的  -是啊
- This your place?  - Yeah.
那你一定就是  "J·馬洛尼"
Then you must be, uh, "J. Maloney."
告訴我  這是代表  嗯  約翰·馬洛尼
Tell me, does that stand for, uh, John orJim?
-喬森  -是的
- Joe.  - Right.
一切正常
Everything's okay.
有趣  嗯  你幾乎不需要任何油
Funny, uh, you didn't hardly need any gas.
不需要加油  我猜你來這裡不是為了車  先生
Didrt need no oil... Guess you didn't come here for the car, huh, mister?
你能幫我擦一下擋風玻璃嗎
Could you get my windshield, please?
沒問題
Don't worry.
你知道一個叫做  艾迪·休奎奇的人嗎
You wouldn't happen to know a guy by the name of Edward Shoebridge, would ya?
以前住在這一邊
Used to live around here.
這名字我沒印象
Name don't ring no bell with me.
為什麼你要問這個  嗯  他叫什麼  休奎奇
What would you be wantir with this, uh, what's his name, uh, Shoebridge?
是啊  法律問題
Yeah. Legal matter.
-你是律師  -對
- You a lawyer?  - Yeah.
我叫麥克布萊  法蘭克·麥克布萊
Name's McBride. Frank McBride.
我第一次和不需要  我付錢的律師交談
First time I ever talked to a lawyer didn't cost me money.
實際上  馬洛尼先生  和我交談還能讓你賺點錢
Actually, Mr. Maloney, by talking to me you could make yourself some money.
-是嗎  -我願意支付合理的現金
- Yeah?  - I'm prepared to pay a reasonable sum of cash,
立刻付  如果你能提供給我任何  艾迪·休奎奇的資訊
right now, for any information that could lead me to Eddie Shoebridge.
我到任何地方  律師通常是帶來壞消息
Where I come from, lawyers are usually bad news.
喔  不  這次不是  這次會是個好消息
Oh, no. Not this time. This time they're good news.
事實上  我認為艾迪·休奎奇
Matter of fact, I think that Eddie Shoebridge...
會很高興聽到我帶給他的消息
would be delighted when he hears from me.
你要告訴他什麼
What are you gonna tell him?
嗯  我的客戶要求我保密
Well, my client has asked me to keep that confidential.
誰聘請你去找這傢伙
Who hired you to find this guy?
-這也得保密  -我當然希望能幫你  先生
- That's confidential also.  - Sure like to help you, Mister...
這裡的生意並不太好
Business ain't all that good around here.
-我想你能幫我  -是嗎
- I think you can help me.  - Is that right?
嗯  這裡的人們告訴我  艾迪·休奎奇已經死了
Mm-hmm. See, people around here have been telling me that Eddie Shoebridge is dead.
如果他死了  看來他就聽不到
Well, if he's dead, looks like he ain't gonna be hearir...
你要告訴他的好消息了  嗯
all that good news you have to tell him, huh?
我認為他還活著
I think he's alive.
看來這輛車不需要太乾淨了
Sure don't keep this car very clean.
你能告訴我  為什麼要在空墳上  安置墓碑嗎  馬洛尼
You want to tell me why you put a headstone on an empty grave, Maloney?
什麼墓碑
What headstone?
一個你付了395美元買的  就在1965年
The one you paid $395 for back in 1965.
你欠我2  47美元  先生
You owe me $2.47, mister.
兩個星期前
Two weeks before that,
你到縣政府申請
you went to the county courthouse...
艾迪·休奎奇的死亡證明
and asked for a certificate of death for Edward Shoebridge,
而且你被拒絕了
and you were turned down.
-你要用信用卡支付嗎  -不
- You wanna give me your credit card?  - No.
信用卡被停用了
Credit cards are out.
跟你一樣  我喜歡付  現金
Like you, I prefer to pay... in cash.
這個是我個人最喜歡的
Now, this one happens to be my personal favorite.
是不是很高雅
Isn't it exquisite?
對我來說太貴了
Probably too expensive for me.
我能幫你嗎  先生
Can I help you, sir?
抱歉  我馬上回來
Excuse me. I'll be right back. Uh, Mrs. Clay?
克萊兒女士  你能幫我  接待一下坎妮安女士嗎
Would you take care of Mrs. Cunningham for a few moments?
好的  亞當森先生
Certainly, Mr. Adamson.
我擔心我太過喜歡了
I'm afraid I rather like it.
嘿  艾迪  你這狗娘養的
Hey, Eddie. You old son of a bitch.
如果對你來說都一樣  我比較喜歡叫亞瑟·亞當森
If it's all the same to you, I prefer Arthur Adamson.
你來這裡幹嘛
Now what in the hell are you doing here?
有要緊的事找你  就這樣  艾迪  亞瑟
Had to see you about something kind of urgent. That's all, Eddie... Arthur.
-你就不能打電話給我嗎  -有些事不能在電話裡談
- Couldrt you have phoned me?  - Some things you don't put on no telephone.
嘿  你有酒嗎
Hey, uh, you got any booze around?
好吧  喬森  這次是什麼事
All right, Joseph. What is it this time?
要買新的冰箱給你老婆
New freezer for your wife?
老媽要做另一個手術  賭徒威脅要殺你  還是什麼
Mother needs another operation? Bookies threatened to kill you? What?
嘿  艾迪  你把我說得好像寄生蟲
Aw, come on, Eddie. You make me sound like some kind of sponger.
我不是不感激你的幫助
Not that I ain't grateful for all your favors.
-我有得選擇嗎  -好了  好了  就這樣
- Did I ever have a choice?  - Okay, okay. Here it is.
首先  我得問你一個問題
First off, I gotta ask you a question.
-問吧  -我問你  別廢話  艾迪
- Go ahead.  - I'm tellir ya. No shit now, Eddie.
你能想到什麼理由  這麼多年後
Can you think of any reason why anyone would be sniffir around in your life...
怎麼會有人對你的生活感興趣
after all these years?
我想不出任何理由  怎麼了
I can't think of any reason at all. Why?
今天有個傢伙來到車廠
Well, there's this guy comes around the garage today...
探問艾迪·休奎奇
tryir to locate Eddie Shoebridge.
他自稱是個律師  有個好消息帶給你
Claims he's a lawyer, he's got good news for ya.
沒說是什麼事  為誰工作
Wort say what, or who he's workir for.
只說他叫麥克布萊  我第一眼看到他就知道是說謊
Calls himself McBride. I know he's a phony the minute I see him.
-警察  -不  是業餘的
- Police?  - No way. He's a real amateur.
我追查他的車牌
I traced his license plates with the bureau...
也不是開他自己的車
Doesrt even drive his own car.
"布蘭琪·泰勒  城堡大道17號"
"Blanche Tyler, 17 Castle Heights Road."
-他長什麼樣子  -高瘦  大約35歲
- What did he look like?  - He's tall, thin, about 35.
他叼著一支煙斗  問許多自以為是的問題
He's always got a pipe on. Asking a lot of smart-ass questions.
-你告訴他什麼了  -什麼該死的都沒說
- What'd you tell him?  - Nothir. Not a goddamn thing.
我不需要說  他什麼都知道
I didn't have to. He knew everything...
你叫我幫你立的假墓碑
fake headstone you had me put up,
我如何試圖幫你申請死亡證明
how I tried to get you officially declared dead.
那狗娘養的還說了  他認為你還活著
The son of a bitch says he thinks you're still alive.
他在找你  艾迪
He's lookir for you, Eddie.
任何一個狗娘養的想找到你
And any son of a bitch who's lookir for you...
就會找上我
is lookir for me.
哦
Well,
無論他有什麼行動  他不會找到我的
whatever he's up to, he won't find me.
你太過擔心了  喬森
You worry too much, Joseph.
是呀  我太過擔心  因為你只是策劃放火
Yeah, I worry too much, because you only planned the fire,
把老先生和老太太鎖在臥房裡
and locked your old man and old lady in the bedroom.
-是我淋汽油  我點燃抹布  -我很感謝你
- I poured the gasoline. I lit the rags.  - And I thank you.
那是我不光彩的童年當中  最快樂的一天
The happiest day of my whole, inglorious childhood.
好吧  你想繼續當孩子  我有我的做法
All right, you want to kid about it, it's all right with me.
-我要跟蹤這傢伙  -然後呢
- I'm gonna track this guy down.  - And then what?
這個
This.
-你永遠不會改變  是嗎  -你有沒有理由抱怨
- You'll never change, will you?  - You got no cause to complain.
當你需要我  我總是在那裡
- When you needed me, I was always there, wasrt I?
聽著  把那東西拿開
- Look, put that thing away.
聽我說  我要你回巴洛溪
And listen to me. I want you to go back to Barlow Creek.
什麼都別做  什麼都別說
Do nothing, say nothing.
讓我自己來解決這件事  用平靜的方式
Let me look into this matter in my own, quiet way.
如果我需要你  我會和你聯絡
And if I need you for anything, I'll contact you.
好嗎
Okay?
你是老闆  亞瑟
You're the boss, Arthur.
這很感人不是嗎  一個完美的謀殺
Isn't it touching how... a perfect murder...
使我們的友誼  這些年來一直維繫著
has kept our friendship alive all these years?
你最好相信
You better believe it.
抱歉  打擾了  亞當森先生
I'm sorry to disturb you, Mr. Adamson.
有兩位先生找您  從警局來的
There are two gentlemen here to see you, from the police department.
告訴他們  我馬上來
Tell them I'll be right out.
老天  艾迪
Jesus Christ, Eddie!
在這兒等著
Wait here.
-我是亞瑟·亞當森  能為您效勞  -抱歉  打擾您
- Arthur Adamson. What can I do for you gentlemen?  - Sorry to bother you.
我是安迪·布希檢察官  這位是彼得森副官
Andy Bush, Bureau of Inspectors, and this is Lieutenant Peterson.
-嗨  -我的榮幸
- Hi.  - My pleasure.
毫無疑問  你一定讀過或聽說過  康斯坦丁綁架案
No doubt you've been reading, or hearing, about the Constantine kidnapping.
哦  我必須承認  檢察官
Well, I have a confession to make, Inspector.
當我聽到那寶石的大小  我都流口水了
When I heard of the size of that stone, my mouth watered.
專業來說
Professionally speaking, of course.
希望你不要感到受歧視  亞當森先生
Well, just so you don't feel discriminated against, Mr. Adamson,
我們只是對城裡的每個珠寶商  和銀樓做例行性詢問
we're routinely covering every gem dealer and jewelry store in the city.
哦  我受寵若驚
Well, I'm flattered.
你有許多機會去接觸  有注意到什麼不尋常嗎
Have you, by any chance, noticed anything out of the ordinary, Mr. Adamson?
有任何異常的大小寶石
Any unusual movement of large... or small...
在過去幾天流入市面
stones into the markets these last few days?
-絕對沒有  -我明白了
- Absolutely not.  - I see.
我認為你們可以假設這個  嗯
I take it that you're going on the assumption...
"贓物"已經被切割成較小的寶石
that this, uh, "ransom stone" has been cut up into smaller gems?
-有道理  先生  -這樣更有銷路
- That's correct, sir.  - It makes a lot of sense.
我們也是這麼認為
We think so.
如果可以  恕我冒昧地提出一項建議
If I may presume to make a suggestion,
在我看來  你們應該涵蓋  古董商和二手珠寶市場
it seems to me you ought to be covering the antique and secondhand jewelry markets.
他們從任何人那裡購買  而我們只向專業珠寶批發商買貨
They buy from anyone, whereas we jewelers buy exclusively on the wholesale exchanges.
-我們已經這麼做了  亞當森先生  -喔
- That's already being done, Mr. Adamson.  - Oh!
我認為我們已經佔用  亞當森先生太多時間了
I think we've taken up enough of Mr. Adamsors time.
很抱歉  我沒能給你們  太多的幫助
Well, I'm sorry I haven't been able to be of more help to you.
不過  如果我有聽到任何  不尋常的市場交易
However, if I do hear of any unusual transactions in the marketplace,
我一定會與您聯繫
I'll be sure and contact you.
-好的  不勝感激  再見  -保重
- Yes, we'd appreciate that. Much obliged.  - Take care.
-再見  先生  -祝你們好運
- Good-bye, sir.  - Good day. And good luck!
克萊兒女士  你可以關門了  我還有一些工作要做
Mrs. Clay, close up as soon as you wish. I have some work to do in here.
我會從後門離開
I'll let myself out the back way.
-晚安  -晚安
- Good night.  - Good night.
-你的朋友布蘭琪·泰勒是個靈媒  -靈媒
- Your friend, Blanche Tyler, is a spiritualist.  - A spiritualist?
招牌上是這麼寫的  但沒有人在家
That's what it says on her shingle. Also, there's no one home.
靈魂是永遠不會在家的  上車
A spirit is never at home. Get in.
你認為我們該怎麼辦
What do you think we should do?
我們等待  我們仍然不知道那男的是誰
We'll wait. We still don't know who the man is yet.
-非抽不可  -嗯哼
- Must you?  - Mm-hmm.
那一定是她
That must be her.
那個叼著煙斗的  肯定就是去找馬洛尼的人
That must be the fellow with the pipe who called on Maloney.
一個計程車司機
A cab driver.
魯尼  魯尼  怎麼回事  你要去哪兒
Lumley. Lumley, what's this? Where are ya goir?
我要回家躺在自己的床上  可以好好睡個覺
I'm going home to my own bed where I can get some sleep.
不  你不會的
No, you're not.
布蘭琪  你不能每件事  都要順著你的意
Blanche, is that all you've ever got on your mind?
你留著要幹嘛  未雨綢繆
What are you saving it for, a rainy day?
親愛的  你永遠不會知道  什麼時候會需要它
Honey, you never know when you're gonna need it.
你很不體貼  魯尼
You're not being friendly, Lumley.
布蘭琪  我已經精疲力盡了  我對你是沒利用價值的
Blanche, I'm too pooped to pop. I'd be useless to you.
你對我總是毫無用處
You're always useless to me!
當我需要你時  你總是精疲力盡
You're always pooping out when I need you!
我們可以賺一大筆錢  你說這是毫無用處
we can collect a huge sum of money, You call that useless?
你知道我在說什麼  來  進屋吧  別吵了
You know what I'm talking about. Come on in side and stop being difficult.
今晚不行  我不會留在這兒
Not tonight, Josephine. I'm outta here.
你這個懶蟲
You're a fink!
如果我是懶蟲  你就是一個忘恩負義的婊子
If I'm a fink, you're an ungrateful bitch.
-那明天呢  -怎樣
- What about tomorrow?  - What about it?
你有重要的工作要做  我要你確認誰是艾迪·休奎
You've got important work to do. I want you to be sure about Eddie Shoe...
跟他說
Talk to him!
你要告訴我多少次
How many times are you going to tell me that?
我又要告訴你多少次  我明天的工作是開計程車
How many times am I gonna have to tell you that tomorrow I have to work in my cab?
所以要等到禮拜天
So it'll wait till Sunday.
你最好給我一個簡要  我一頭霧水
You better give me a quick synopsis. I'm confused.
很簡單  一個疲憊的計程車司機
Simple. A cab driver is shacked up...
和一個性飢渴的靈媒  布蘭琪·泰勒
with a sex-starved medium named Blanche Tyler.
別問我為什麼  但很顯然
Don't ask me why, but apparently they're on the trail...
他們找到了艾迪·休奎奇的幽靈
of some spook named Eddie Shoebridge.
幸運的是  不是在追蹤  你最喜歡的"贓物"和我
Fortunately, not on the trail of your favorite kidnapper and mine.
你怎麼能那麼肯定
How can you be so sure?
你也聽到了  他們談論到將賺一大筆錢
You did hear him talk about collecting a huge hunk of money.
那報酬不是在我們頭上
Couldrt that be the reward that's on our heads?
你說到重點了  法蘭西大姊
You got yourself a point there, Frances, old girl.
只有時間才能告訴我們  是好是壞
Only time will tell whether it's any good.
但有一件事是肯定的
One thing's certain.
我們不會改變我們的計劃  不會是現在
We're not going to change our game plan. Not now.
買瓶酒給我  亞瑟
Buy me a drink, Arthur.
一輛閃亮的車
A shiny car.
一輛豪華轎車
A... limousine?
他為什麼要開得這麼快  亨利
Why does he drive so fast, Henry?
那是什麼  在他旁邊座位上的
What's that? On the seat beside him?
我聽到嬰兒的哭聲  快  亨利  在他消失前
I hear the sound of a baby crying. Quick, Henry, before he disappears.
問他  是的  我明白
Ask...Yes, I know.
我  看到他了
I...see him now.
穿著制服  一個司機
The uniform. A chauffeur.
什麼  亨利  我要聽他說話
What? Henry, I need words.
誰  什麼
Who? The what?
蘭伯特家的司機
The Rainbird chauffeur?
天哪  老麥克·歐基夫  我們的司機
Good heavens. Old Michael O'Keefe, our chauffeur.
麥克要去哪裡
Where is Michael going?
亨利  問他把哈麗葉的嬰兒  帶去哪裡
Henry, ask him where he's taking Harriet's baby.
噢  有太多影像  閃得太快了
Oh, more pictures are coming in too fast.
我看不清楚
I can hardly make them out.
亨利  墓地  一個墓碑
Henry, a graveyard, a headstone?
我不喜歡這樣  亨利
I don't like this, Henry.
鞋子  橋
A shoe. Bridge.
鞋子橋  噢  不要這樣對我  亨利
A shoe bridge? Oh, don't do this to me, Henry.
-對司機說話  -噢  上帝  有東西在燃燒
- Speak to the chauffeur.  - Oh, God, something's burning.
是房子  快  亨利  房子著火了
The house. Quick, Henry. The house is on fire.
帶我離開這裡
Take me away from here.
我不想看這些
I don't want to see this.
我受不了他們可怕的尖叫聲
I can't bear the sound of their awful screaming.
回到司機那裡  亨利  讓麥克加入我們
Go back to the chauffeur, Henry. Get Michael into our presence.
蘭伯特女士記得他
Miss Rainbird remembers him.
是的  我記得
Yes, I remember.
布蘭琪夫人  讓我來說
Madame Blanche, listen to me.
你能聽到我嗎
Can you hear me?
我想起一件事  這非常重要
I've remembered something else that could be terribly important.
等一下  亨利  在你走之前
Wait one minute, Henry. Before you go,
蘭伯特女士需要知道  哈麗葉孩子的情況
Miss Rainbird deserves some kind of assurance about Harriet's child.
他現在是個大人了
He's a man by now,
我們想知道他現在快樂嗎
and we have to know, is he happy, Henry?
他還活著嗎  過得幸福嗎
Is he alive and well and happy?
如果你不能
If you can't, you can't.
我當然不能強迫你
I certainly can't force you.
是  當然  她會理解的
Yes. Of course she'll understand.
直到下一次  那麼  再見了
Until next time, then. Good-bye.
再見  親愛的
Good-bye, my love.
-發生什麼事  -難道你不記得了
- What happened?  - Don't you remember?
-並不太愉快  -噢  沒關係了
- Not a blessed thing.  - Oh, it doesn't matter now.
聽著  聽著  布蘭琪夫人
Listen, listen, Madame Blanche.
你的亨利拾回了  我完全遺忘的記憶
Your Henry jogged my memory of something I'd completely forgotten.
當我們可憐的老司機麥克  意識到他即將死亡時
When our poor old chauffeur, Mike, realized he was dying,
他寫信給我  說世上有個人
he wrote to me and said there was one person on earth...
他許下承諾說
who had promised that he'd make it his business...
只要他還活著  就能夠知道哈麗葉的兒子在哪兒
to know where Harriet's son was as long as he lived.
是個牧師  幫新生嬰兒洗禮的
It was the parson who baptized the newborn baby.
還有一件事我要告訴你
And there's an additional thing I can tell you.
別告訴我  讓我猜猜看
Don't tell me. Let me guess.
-500美元  -沒錢  連100也沒有
- Five hundred.  - Not a penny. Not even a hundred for expenses.
這是全有或全無  喬治
It's all or nothing, George,
直到我可以找出  他的名字和現在的住址
until I can produce his name and his present address.
-老天  布蘭琪  -不過  她給了我一條重大線索
- Jesus, Blanche.  - However, she gave me a marvelous clue.
-我們又來了  -不  是你有得忙了
- Here we go again.  - No, here you go again...
有一個人可以告訴你  休奎奇是生是死
to the man who might tell you if Shoebridge is dead or alive.
-那是誰  -聖安塞爾姆大教堂的伍德主教
- Who's that?  - Bishop Wood at St. Anselm's Cathedral.
-老天爺  布蘭琪  -不  喬治  不是祂
- Holy Christ, Blanche.  - No, George, not him.
是聖安塞爾姆大教堂的伍德主教
Bishop Wood at St. Anselm's Cathedral.
他曾經是一個牧師  替嬰兒時期的休奎奇受洗過
He was a parson once and he baptized the Shoebridge baby.
打擾一下
Excuse me.
抱歉
Sorry.
你知道我要怎樣  才能約見伍德主教
Do you know how I could, uh, make a date to see Bishop Wood?
如果你想今天約見  你必須先找牧師
If you want to make the appointment today, you'll have to make it through the chaplain.
哪一個是牧師
Which one is the chaplain?
禮拜結束後  我會帶你去的
When the service is over, I'll show you where to go.
噢  親愛的
Oh, dear.
你知道他還在動  你確定給他的用量足夠
You know he's moving. You sure you gave him enough?
只是一般的劑量  他看起來無害
Just the usual dose. He looks so harmless.
當我還是個孩子時  住在這個村莊
When I was a little kid living in that village,
他總是讓我覺得  我是個邪惡的東西
he always made me feel like I was something evil.
-看看我現在  -我覺得年輕了幾歲
- And look at me now.  - I feel years younger.
你知道  多一個像這樣的今天  我們將一臉土灰
You know, one more like this one today, and we'll be naturally gray.
這是一個令人難以置信的工作  我真的認為這超過100萬
It was an incredible job. I really think it's won'th more than a million.
抱歉  親愛的  但我可不想回去  重寫我的贖金紙條
I'm sorry, darling, but I'm not going back...
那將背離了我的祈禱書
and rewrite my ransom note that I left in my prayer book.
你必須好好動一動  去解決這100萬
You'll have to be a good sport and settle for a million.
你很漂亮  法蘭  很漂亮
You were beautiful, Fran. Just beautiful.
-我很害怕  -我告訴過你沒問題的  不是嗎
- I was scared.  - I told you it'd be all right, didn't I?
人們在教堂是很守禮節的
People in church are inibited.
他們不會跳起來亂跑  或是製造噪音
They don't jump up and run around and make a lot of noise.
他們都虔誠有禮
They're all too religiously polite.
我們要繼續自我陶醉  或是你想談談他呢
Shall we go on congratulating ourselves, or would you like to talk about him now?
-誰  -誰
- Who?  - "Who."
那個叼著煙斗的男人
The man with the pipe.
-你看到他在那裡  -如影隨形
- So you saw him there, huh?  - Larger than life.
比死亡還難纏
Larger than death, you mean.
他現在追求的毫無疑問了
There's no doubt about who he's after now.
你打算怎麼處理他  親愛的
What were you planning to do about him, dear,
除了不想告訴我的以外
besides just not telling me?
我不打算對他做任何事情
I'm not planning to do anything about him.
喬森·馬洛尼渴望的那份工作  現在他得到了
Joe Maloney's been itching for that job. He's got it.
我會打電話給他  等我把我們的客人安置好後
I'll phone him as soon as we put our guest in his quarters.
我說得對  那計程車司機真傻
I was right about that silly cab driver.
在我的生命裡  這次我討厭說對了
For once in my life I hate being right.
他怎麼會知道我們要去那裡
Well, how in the hell could he have known we were going to be there...
除了你和我  世上還有誰會知道
when you and I are the only two people in the world who knew that?
我有一個想法
I've got a thought.
-就是有點愚蠢  -說吧
- It's a dumb one.  - Say it.
你相信特異功能嗎
Do you believe in E.S.P.?
特異功能  超常的心靈現象
Extra sensory perception, all that psychic phenomena?
什麼意思  是說那個叫什麼的夫人
What do you mean? Madame What's-her-name?
布蘭琪·泰勒
Blanche Tyler.
老天
Jesus.
你和我都知道這一面牆  但我們能犯錯嗎
You and I know that that's off the wall, but, uh, can we afford to be wrong?
恐怕我們的那對歡喜冤家  將會共同發生一起致命的事故
I'm afraid our two quarrelsome lovers are going to have to share a fatal accident.
噢  我的天啊
Oh, my God.
但馬洛尼不會這麼做的  對吧
But Maloney wouldn't be willing to do that, would he?
當然  他會很樂意做的
Of course he'd be willing. Gladly.
他會相信那是為了保護自己  和他的老夥伴
He'd believe he was protecting himself and his old buddy.
我不想知道  好嗎
I don't want to know about it. Okay?
-答應我  亞瑟  -拜託  親愛的
- Promise me, Arthur.  - Come on, now, dear.
這有什麼好激動的
That's what's so exciting about all of this.
我們同生共死  沒有什麼好退縮的
We move as one. Everything together. Nothing held back.
這是嚴重的疏失  就這樣失去他  他是我們的所有
It was gross negligence, losing him that way. He was all we had.
我沒有失去他  他只是被綁架
I didn't lose him. He was kidnapped.
為什麼會有人對主教幹這種事
Why would anyone want to do that to a bishop?
為了贖金啊  傻瓜  那可是100萬美元
For the ransom, dummy. It's a million dollars.
我無能為力  你知道  我就在那兒
I can't get over it. You know, I was right there.
噢  忘了那100萬吧  我們的一萬該怎麼辦
Tsk. Oh, forget about the million. What about out 10,000?
我們現在無路可走  魯尼
We've got nowhere to go now, Lumley.
我該怎麼告訴蘭伯特女士
What am I gonna tell Miss Rainbird?
看來我和亨利又得費盡心力
I suppose Henry and I are going to have to exhaust ourselves
來補原本該是你的工作
again doing your work for you.
什麼意思  我的工作  我的工作是駕駛該死的計程車
What d'ya mean, my work? My work is driving a goddamn cab, for Christ's sake.
看在上帝的分上  從這一分鐘開始  做點正確的
And startir right this minute, that's exact...
-正確的什麼  繼續說  -接電話
- That's exact what? Go ahead.  - Answer the telephone.
哈羅  誰
Hello? Who?
馬洛尼先生
Mr. Maloney?
巴洛溪  請繼續
Barlow Creek? Go ahead.
哈羅
Hello.
你能說大聲一點嗎  馬洛尼先生
Can you speak a little louder, Mr. Maloney?
我說我透過你那律師朋友
I said I traced you through the license plates on
駕駛的車牌號碼追查到你
that car your lawyer friend was driving.
我猜你仍然想尋找艾迪·休奎奇
I figured if you was still lookir for some dope on Eddie Shoebridge,
-我可以給你一點情報  -哦
- I might have somethir for you.  - Oh.
你為什麼改變主意了  馬洛尼先生
How come you changed your mind, Mr. Maloney?
我沒和你的人說
I didn't say nothir to your man
是因為我覺得不關我的事
'cause I felt it was none of my business and none of his,
但我一直在想  我可以因此賺點外快
but I been thinkir about it and how I could use the bread.
因此考慮過後  我願意帶你去見一個人
So for a little consideration, I'm willing to lead you to someone...
他認識艾迪·休奎奇的太太
who knows Eddie Shoebridge's wife.
你得付一大筆錢
It'll cost you a grand.
喔  別傻了  馬洛尼先生
Oh, don't be silly, Mr. Maloney.
我的律師就在我的身邊
I have my lawyer right here beside me,
他說願意付你100美元  只要能找到人
and he says he'll give you $100 provided it leads to something. Make it two.
喔  好吧  成交
Oh... All right. It's a deal.
-我們在哪碰面  -你和你的律師朋友
- Where do we meet?  - You and that lawyer friend of yours,
你們開車來  兩個小時後在梅布斯見面
you drive up and meet me at Abe and Mabel's in two hours.
-梅布斯  -是路邊咖啡屋  在榭爾曼路上
- Abe and Mabel's?  - It's a cafe up the road to Mt. Sherman,
進入22號公路後大約五英哩  你知道哪裡嗎
about five miles off Route 22. You know where it is?
知道  為什麼到那麼遠  我們不能找個更方便的地方嗎
Yeah. Why so far away? Can't we meet somewhere more convenient?
我要帶你去的派對就在那邊
This party I'm gonna take you to happens to be up in that area.
我明白了  馬洛尼先生  你肯定艾迪·休奎奇還活著
I see. Mr. Maloney, are you admitting Edward Shoebridge is still alive?
兩個小時後  我看到白花花的鈔票再說
I ain't sayir a thing till I see the color of your money, in two hours.
-你怎麼想  -我聞到魚腥味
- What d'ya think?  - Smells fishy to me.
我知道
I know.
但是當你快餓死時  甚至魚腥味都會覺得好
But even fish smells good when you're starving to death.
我們會有什麼損失  他是唯一的線索
What have we got to lose? He's the only clue left.
你有200美元嗎
You got $200 on you?
你比我更清楚
You know me better than that.
當然沒有  再給我一個
Of course not. Fix me another one of these.
你不需要  你已經有一個了
You don't need another one. You already got one.
我們只有兩個小時去那裡
We only got two hours to get there.
-我要在車上吃  -走吧
- I'll eat it in the car.  - Come on.
你真難應付
You're impossible.
兩杯啤酒  麻煩
A couple of beers, please.
他遲到了
He must be late.
謝謝
Thank you, dear.
孩子們  去坐那邊
You kids sit over there.
-哦  今天週日的學校如何  -吵死了
- How was Sunday school today?  - Noisy.
-五瓶可樂  麻煩  -我們沒有吵啊
- Five Cokes, please.  - We didn't make any noise.
這就對了  所以你才在這裡
That's right. That's why you're here.
不要怪我
Don't blame me.
我有說什麼嗎
Did I say anything?
-你好  抱歉  我遲到了  -我幫你搬張椅子
- Hello. I'm sorry I'm late.  - I'll get you a chair.
-沒關係  我坐這兒  -我和你坐一起
- That's all right. I'll sit over here.  - I'll join you.
瞧  好手段
Look at that. Nice arrangement.
別下流了  喬治
Don't be obscene, George.
喔
Oh.
謝謝  親愛的
Thank you, my dear.
讓頭腦保持清醒  好嗎
Just see that you keep you head screwed on straight, will you?
他不會來了
He's not coming.
噢  就這樣結束了
Well, that's the end of that.
喬治  在急什麼
George, what's the big hurry?
開慢一點  好嗎
Just slow down a little, will ya, please?
我說了別開那麼快  喬治
I told you not to drive so fast, George!
我不知道怎麼回事  油門好像卡住了
I don't know what's wrong. The accelerator seems to be sticking.
喬治  看在老天的份上  開慢點  好嗎
George, for God's sake, slow up, will ya?
我做不到
I can't.
我的漢堡快要吐出來了
My hamburger's coming up.
油門  卡住了
The accelerator... is stuck.
踩煞車
Use the brakes!
-沒反應  -什麼
- They don't work.  - What?
-煞車沒反應  -什麼意思
- The brakes don't work.  - What do you mean?
-喬治  -拜託  別抓我  看在老天的份上
- George!  - Come on, woman. Don't grab me, for God's sake!
不是我  是煞車壞了
It's not me. It's the brakes don't work.
我快得心臟病了  喬治
I'm getting violently ill, George.
-你快讓我窒息了  布蘭琪  老天  -喬治
- You're chokir me, Blanche, for Christ's sake!  - George!
快想辦法
Do something!
拉手煞車  伸手拉手煞車
Grab the brake! Reach down and pull the hand brake.
-快拉  -我在拉了
- Pull on it!  - I am pulling!
你的手別抓方向盤  快拉
Get your hands off the steering wheel. Pull on it!
-我在拉了  -快拉
- I am pulling.  - Pull it.
快啊
Come on.
你的手別抓方向盤  該死的
Get your hand off the goddamn wheel!
我得離開這條路
I gotta get off this road.
布蘭琪  堅持住
Blanche, just hang on.
有趣嗎
Wasrt that fun?
-去你的  喬治·魯尼  -你吃錯藥啦
- Damn you, George Lumley!  - What's the matter with you?
-不是我  是馬洛尼  -開車的不是他
- It was't me. It's Maloney.  - He was't driving!
那當然  是他對車動了手腳  弄壞了煞車
Of course, but he screwed up the car and broke the brakes.
-馬洛尼  -沒錯
- Maloney?  - Yes.
你認為這是巧合  布蘭琪
You think it's a coincidence, Blanche?
嗯
Huh?
你的車  可能要大修幾天了
Your car... is gonna be out of commission for a couple days.
我們想個辦法回家吧
So let's go find us another way to get home.
喬治  你沒事吧
George. Are you all right?
嗯  我想是吧  你呢
Mm-hmm. I think so. How about you?
我很好  對不起
I'm okay. I'm sorry.
-你真的認為馬洛尼要我們死  -嗯哼
- Do you really think Maloney wanted us dead?  - Mm-hmm.
為什麼  老天  為何有人會想這樣對我們
Why, in the name of God, would anyone want to do that to us?
我不知道
I don't know,
但可以打賭  肯定和你那個  神秘的朋友艾迪·休奎奇有關
but you can bet is has something to do with your mysterious friend, Eddie Shoebridge.
或許馬洛尼就把他埋在他家後院
Maloney's probably got him buried in his backyard.
不希望被我們給找到
Doesrt want us to find out.
那邊
That way.
你好  抱歉  遲到了
Hi there. Sorry I'm late.
恭喜你對我們的車幹的好事  做得很完美  馬洛尼
Congratulations on the nice job you did on our car, Maloney.
為什麼你們倆要站在路中間
What are you two doir standir in the middle of the road?
你明知我們為何站在路上  馬洛尼
You know perfectly well what we're doing on the road, Maloney.
你一定就是布蘭琪·泰勒  很高興見到你  你的車子呢
You must be Blanche Tyler. Pleased to meet ya. Where's your car?
這麼說吧  它不太聽話  你明白我的意思吧
Let's just say it ain't in runnir order, you know what I mean?
上車  我載你們到最近的車站
Hop in. I'll give ya a lift to the nearest station.
不  謝了  我們不坐靈車
No, thank you. We don't ride in hearses.
你以為我是來這裡玩的
You think I came up here for the fun of it?
是你要我帶你去派對  那人認識艾迪·休奎奇的太太啊
Then you want me to take you to this party that knows Eddie Shoebridge's wife.
你為什麼不繼續前進  自己走吧  馬洛尼  我們當沒看到
Why don't you just go ahead, uh, by yourself this time, Maloney. We'll skip it.
他真是迷人
He's all charm.
那是誰
Who's that?
是馬洛尼  他跟著我們
That's Maloney. He's after us.
快點
Come on.
嘿  夥計們  我們快閃
Hey, guys, let's get the hell outta here.
我們最好通知警察
We better get the police.
然後損失我們的一萬美元
And lose our $10,000?
我能幫你嗎  夫人
May I be of some help to you, madam?
-我想看一些手鐲  -要特定款式嗎
- I'd like to see some bracelets.  - Any particular kind?
你有綠寶石或珍珠的嗎
Do you have anything with turquoise, or perhaps pearls?
-我們的客人還好嗎  -他很好
- Anything wrong with our houseguest?  - He's fine.
我給了他一頓豐盛的午餐  和一瓶新產的紅酒
I gave him a very nice lunch and a fresh bottle of wine.
-或許這其中一條會吸引你  -這些是海洋珍珠
- Maybe one of these will appeal to you?  - Are those seed pearls?
是的
That's right.
-你來這裡幹嘛  -這些看起來像淡水珍珠
- What are you doing here?  - These look like freshwater pearls.
有消息傳來
The message has come through on KFAG.
他們已經準備好  我們所提出的寶石了
They've located the stone we asked for.
在紐約溫士頓
In New York. Harry Winston.
53克拉
Fifty-three carats.
這些都很好  多少錢
These are very nice. How much are they?
315美元  含稅
$315, including tax.
我們什麼時候行動
When do we make the pickup?
明晚9:30
Tomorrow night, 9:30.
好的  現在回家吧
Good. Now go on home.
你能不能把這些先預留下來
Would it be possible for you to set these aside...
以便我可以帶丈夫過來看看
so that I can bring in my husband and he can look at them?
當然可以  夫人
Of course, madam.
還有一個壞消息
Now for the bad news.
看看這個
Take a look at this.
沒用的廢物  他搞砸了
Incompetent bastard. He blew it.
現在我們得自己去幹掉他們
Now we'll have to eliminate these two ourselves.
-我們  -沒錯
- Ourselves?  - That's right.
明晚  等我們把客人送走後
Tomorrow night, right after we return our guest.
-我不行  -你必須做
- I can't.  - You must.
記著  共謀等同於主謀
Remember: Share and share alike.
你別說了  別說了
You stop it! Stop it!
-決定了嗎  -這個好
- Decide on something?  - That'll be fine.
我要這一個
I'll have it wrapped.
但不僅如此  遠遠不止於此
But it was more than that, much more than that...
你留下了生命中珍貴的禮物
that you left behind as your precious gift to life.
是的  喬森·馬洛尼  你是一個慷慨的人
Yes, Joseph Maloney, you were a generous man.
你獻出了你的心和靈魂
You gave of your heart and soul.
你獻出了最好的你
You gave the very best that was in you,
凡世上無人比你付出的更多
and no more than that can be asked of mortal man on this earth.
你深愛你的妻子
You loved your wife dearly.
你給予你親愛的母親和父親
You bestowed upon your dear mother and father...
所有的照料  所有的關心
all the care, all the attention,
在他們的晚年  給予他們需要的耐心和安慰
patience and comfort that they needed... in the sunset of their lives.
我們這些留下的人們
And those of us who are left behind...
為你而哀傷  喬森
to grieve for you, Joseph,
只能遵從上帝的決定
can only bow to the divine judgement of our Lord,
誰選擇了帶你遠離我們
who has chosen to take you away from us...
在一場殘酷的意外
in this cruel accident.
喔  神聖偉大的主啊
Oh, how great the holiness of our God.
祂擁有一切智慧
For He knoweth all things.
祂無所不知
And there is not anything save He knows it.
祂來到了這個世界
And He cometh into the world...
祂可以拯救世人  如果他們能去傾聽祂的聲音
that He may save all men if they will harken unto His voice.
因為祂看到了世人遭受的痛苦
For behold, He suffered that the pains of all men.
是的  每一個活著的生命  都在遭受痛苦
Yea, the pains of every living creature,
男人  女人和孩童
both men, women and children...
你就不能讓我獨自一人嗎
Can't you leave me alone?
你殺了他還不夠嗎
Isn't it enough that you killed him?
並非如此  馬洛尼太太  事情正好相反
That's not so, Mrs. Maloney. It was the other way.
是你  是你來這裡之後  開始了一切
You. You started it all coming here...
並且在你那交易中  把事情搞得一團糟
and messing in things that were none of your business.
請走開  拜託
Now go away. Please!
-馬洛尼太太  我要和你談談  -他已經死了  埋葬了
- Mrs. Maloney, I have to talk to you.  - He's dead and buried.
-沒有什麼可談的  -他為什麼不想要我
- There's nothing to talk about.  - Why didn't he want me...
-尋找艾迪·休奎奇  -我不想聽你說話
- Iooking for Eddie Shoebridge?  - I am not listening to you.
-離開我  -馬洛尼太太  你丈夫要殺我
- Get away from me!  - Mrs. Maloney, your husband tried to kill me,
-你也有份  是嗎  -不
- and you were in on it, werert you?  - No.
-那為何總是逃避我  那就是原因  -不
- Then why are you always running away from me? Is that why?  - No.
你知道你是企圖謀殺的共犯嗎
Do you realize that you are an accessory to an attempted murder?
-與我無關  -也許警方會認為你也有份
- I had nothing to do with that.  - Perhaps the police would think that you did.
-你要我去跟警察說嗎  -看在老天的份上
- You want me to go to the police about it?  - For God's sake.
-你不會那樣  -告訴我艾迪·休奎奇在哪兒
- You wouldn't do that...  - Just tell me where is Eddie Shoebridge?
-我不能  -馬洛尼太太  他在哪  請告訴我
- I can't.  - Mrs. Maloney, where is he? Please tell me.
沒有艾迪·休奎奇
There is no Eddie Shoebridge.
他如煙霧般25年前來到這都市
He went up in smoke 25 years ago and came down in the city.
他自稱亞瑟·亞當森
He calls himself Arthur Adamson.
亞瑟·亞當森
Arthur Adamson?
如果他發現我告訴了你  他會殺了我
If he finds out I told you, he'll kill me.
走開吧  別再靠近我了
Now go away, and don't ever come near me again.
騙子  騙子
Fake! Fake!
等等  你這是在誇大
Wait a second, now. You're the one that's exaggerating.
不  不  我是失蹤了兩三天  但不可能更多了
No, I'll give you two or three days maybe I missed, but never more than that.
-告訴他這非常重要  -噓
- Tell him it's deeply important.  - Shh!
-硬起來  -為何是我
- Stand up.  - Why me?
是什麼使你認為是我跑超過里程
What makes you think that it's me that ran up all the extra mileage?
那些傢伙如何  賀比或艾爾  值日班的人
What about that little asshole, Herbie, or, uh, Al, the one on the day shift?
我明白了  我會去的
I understand. I'll be there.
是  我保證我會過去
Yes, I promise I'll be there.
答案是不行
The answer's no.
他說我必須輪班  並且我今晚就要上工
He says I must work the shift, and I must work it tonight.
幫我個忙  布蘭琪
And do me a favor, Blanche.
拜託別再給我製造麻煩
Please don't give me a hard time.
你沒有全力去抗爭
You didn't put up much of a fight.
親愛的  聽著  我一直消磨時間在幫你
Honey, look. After all the goofir off I've been doir on your behalf,
我差點就要失去我的駕駛座
I'm within a gnat's eyelash of losir my cab
被踢出公司了
and gettir kicked right out of the company.
魯尼  你真傻  你不需要開計程車
Lumley, you're thick! You won't have to drive a cab...
如果你能把這件事辦好  就能拿到錢啊
if you can get this thing over and done with and collect the money.
"如果"親愛的  你總是對我說如果
"If," darling. You're always givir me ifs.
我不能靠如果吃飯  你也不能
I can't eat ifs and neither can you,
朱莉亞·蘭伯特和你之間的  華爾滋太過遙遠了
while Julia Rainbird and you are waltzir around in the great beyond.
拜託  親愛的  我該做的就是回去工作
Come on, sweetheart. The least I can do is show up for work every now and then.
至少  我不是已經給你  那傢伙的名字了嗎
After all, didn't I give you the guy's name?
但是電話簿裡滿滿的都是  亞瑟·亞當森
But the phone book is full of Arthur Adamsons.
這很簡單  你要做的  就是找出正確的那一個
It's very simple. All you need to do is find out the right one.
那很容易  一個大約40歲
That's a snap. The one that's close to 40 years old...
聽到艾迪·休奎奇這名字  就會顫抖的傢伙
and trembles a little bit at the name Eddie Shoebridge.
-簡單  我們明天來做  -現在做會更好
- Easy. We do that tomorrow.  - Now would be much better.
食物就要到手了  魯尼  拜託你  親愛的
A bird in the hand, Lumley. Please. Oh, sweetheart.
唯一的食物是在我的手上
The only bird that's gonna be in my hand...
我必須遺憾地說
and I'm very sorry to say this...
四點至午夜我必須開車
is a steering wheel from 4:00 to midnight.
好吧  我何時才能得到一個吻
Sure. Why should I get a kiss?
當我開始認為  你不再難以忍受的時候
Just when I was beginning to think you werert impossible.
也許沒有你我也能做到
Maybe I'll do it without you.
絕不可能
The hell you will!
來吧  布蘭琪  拜託
Come on, now. Please.
這個休奎奇惹了許多麻煩  不想被發現
This Shoebridge fellow's gone to a lot of trouble not to be found.
如今你不知道會被捲入  什麼麻煩當中
Now you got no idea what kind of trouble you could get into.
不管是什麼  他會忘了那些事的
Whatever it is, he'll forget about it...
當他聽到他將獲得數百萬時
when he hears about the millions he's coming into.
噢  布蘭琪  拜託
Oh, Blanche, come on.
坐下吧  你漂亮的小  屁股
Just sit down on your pretty little... behind.
我得說  這很
And I must say, it is quite an...
不  這是很吸引人的小屁股
No, it is. Very attractive little behind.
等我  好嗎
Just wait for me, okay?
今晚我回到家  我們會
And tonight when I get home, we will, uh...
很好  好好地商量我們的策略
Right. Very nice. Plot our strategy.
明白我的意思嗎  親愛的
Know what I mean, darlir?
誰需要他
Who needs him.
你不會是亞瑟·亞當森  對吧
You wouldn't be Arthur Adamson, would you?
抱歉
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
哈羅  你是亞瑟·亞當森
Hello. Are you Arthur Adamson?
嘿  亞瑟
Hey, Art!
什麼事
Yeah?
對不起  我們打烊了
I'm sorry. We're just closing.
我知道  我不是要購物  請問亞當森先生在嗎
I understand. I'm not shopping. Is Mr. Adamson around?
-不  他不在  但你可以明天再來  -好的
- I'm afraid not. But if you come back tomorrow...  - All right.
但是為了確認是我要找的  亞當森先生
But just to be sure I have the right Mr. Adamson,
-我猜他是一位年約40歲的紳士  -是的  沒錯
- he is a gentleman of about 40, I trust?  - Yes, that's about right.
噢  整個下午以來  這是第一個令人鼓舞的消息
Oh, that's the first encouraging news I've had all afternoon.
為了不耽誤時間  我到哪裡能找到他
Isn't there someplace I might reach him without delay?
-你是說今晚  -是的
- You mean tonight?  - Yes.
他平常都會直接從這裡回家
Well, he usually goes directly home from here.
但今晚很不幸  因為我想他今天要開個派對
But tonight would be very bad because I believe he's giving a party.
我知道他今天提早離開  是為了這個原因
I know he left unusually early for some such reason.
是不是有什麼我可以幫你轉達的  在明天早上
Isn't there something I can tell him for you in the morning?
-這是私人事情  相當私人  -喔  我明白了
- This is personal. Rather personal.  - Oh, I see.
或是你想留個字條給他
Perhaps you'd like to leave him a note.
-字條  是的  -好的  請這邊走
- A note? Very good.  - Yes. Come this way.
抱歉
Excuse me.
謝謝
Thank you.
有什麼問題嗎
Is anything the matter?
嗯  我只是在想
Uh, I was, uh, just thinking.
與其留字條在這裡
Instead of leaving this note here,
不如這樣會更好  我今晚  就發個電報給亞當森先生
it might be better if I sent Mr. Adamson a telegram tonight.
-能告訴我他的地址嗎  -呃  我不能
- What's his address, please?  - Well, I don't...
沒關係的  我們是朋友
It's all right. We're friends.
-富蘭克林街1001號  -富蘭克林街1001號
- 1001 Franklin Street.  - 1001 Franklin.
非常感謝你  你真是親切
Thank you very much. You've been very kind.
你是摩羯座的嗎
You're a Capricorn, aren't you?
不  我是獅子座
No, I'm a Leo.
我想也是
That's what I thought.
-皮特  嗨  -哈羅  布蘭琪寶貝
- Pete, hi.  - Hello, there, Blanche, baby.
-你有看到喬治嗎  -他幾分鐘前剛離開  很快會回來
- Have you seen George?  - He just left a few minutes ago, but he'll be back.
送四個人到河谷參加派對
Took a party of four out to River Valley.
喔  親愛的  那可能要通宵
Oh, dear. That could take all night.
放輕鬆  有什麼事嗎
Easily. What's up?
-你能幫我傳個話給他嗎  -當然可以
- Would you give him a message for me?  - Sure thing.
-告訴他說我找到他了  -你找到他
- Just tell him I found him.  - You found him?
沒錯  他住在富蘭克林1001號
That's right. He lives at 1001 Franklin.
富蘭克林1001號
1001 Franklin.
那就是他的住所  而我現在就要過去
That's where he lives, and that's where I'm going now.
你找到他了  那就是他的住所  並且你現在就要過去
You found him, and that's where he lives, and that's where you're going now.
-謝謝  皮特  -隨時候勞  布蘭琪
- Thanks, Pete.  - Any time, Blanche.
你要去踩點了
You wanna go over the new pickup spot once again?
我記在心裡
I know it by heart.
你沒問題吧
Are you all right?
-我沒問題  -你確定
- I will be.  - You sure?
必須在9:30前到達  我們走吧
Have to be there at 9:30. Let's get going.
伍德主教  該走了
Bishop Wood, it's time to go.
你有穿上你的法衣嗎
Have you your vestments on?
是的  但我還沒吃完雞
Yes, but I haven't finished the chicken.
對不起  閣下
I'm sorry, Your Excellency.
我要你照以下說的做
Here's what I want you to do.
請把椅子放在房間中央
Place the armchair in the center of the room...
背對著門  坐在椅子上
facing away from the door and seat yourself in it.
你會睡得很安穩
You're going to be comfortably put to sleep.
只是一小段時間
But it'll last only for a short while.
非常感謝你  你想得真周到
Thank you very much. You are most considerate.
當你準備好後  讓我知道
Let me know when you're ready.
順便說一下  我還沒看完那本書
By the way. I haven't quite finished that book...
你讓我看書真好
you were kind enough to let me have.
我想  能讓我帶走嗎
May I, uh, take it along?
好帶走我們的指紋
With our fingerprints on it? Tsk, tsk, tsk.
不錯的嘗試  閣下
Nice try, Your Excellency.
謝謝  不煩你了  我準備好了
Thank you. Don't bother, then. I'm ready.
好的  我會把你的燈熄滅
All right, I'll be turning your light off now.
我們不能遲到  看看是誰  小心點
We mustrt be late. See who it is, and be careful.
是她  那個女人  布蘭琪·泰勒
It's her. That woman. Blanche Tyler.
簡直難以置信
This is incredible!
-計程車司機和她在一起  -只有她
- Is that cab driver with her?  - She's alone.
如果我不是要在35分鐘內辦事
If I didn't have to make this pickup in 35 minutes...
我們應該怎麼做
What are we going to do?
什麼也別做
Nothing!
等一會兒
Until later tonight.
-她不見了  -快點  走吧
- She's gone.  - Come on. Let's go.
快  快  快
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
-我想你說過  -我知道
- I thought you said...  - I know.
-亞當森先生  -看著他
- Mr. Adamson?  - Watch him.
喔  亞當森先生  真幸運  我沒有錯過你
Oh, Mr. Adamson. How lucky I am not to have missed you.
-顯然你沒有聽到我在前門按鈴  -顯然是
- Apparently you didn't hear me at the front door.  - Apparently.
我叫布蘭琪·泰勒  是個通靈師
I am Madame Blanche Tyler, the spiritualist.
晚安  甜心
Good evening, honey.
布蘭琪女士  我能麻煩你
Madame Blanche, I wonder if I might suggest to you to remove
把你的車移開我們的車道嗎
your car from our driveway.
-我們約會快遲到了  -喔  是的
- We're terribly late for an appointment.  - Well, yes.
當你聽到我來的原因  亞當森先生  或者該稱呼休奎奇
When you hear why I've come, Mr. Adamson... Or should I say Shoebridge?
-你就不會介意遲到了  -我親愛的女士
- You won't mind being late at all.  - My dear lady,
-我很清楚你來的原因  -你怎麼知道的
- I know exactly why you've come here.  - How could you?
-你和你的朋友  那個計程車司機  -你認識喬治
- And exactly why you and your friend, that cab driver...  - You know George?
過去幾個星期以來一直在追查我  就好像兩條嗜血的獵犬
Have been sniffing along my trail like two eager bloodhounds these past few weeks.
我沒有這樣想  亞當森先生
I had no idea, Mr. Adamson.
-好吧  布蘭琪女士  你找到我了  -真是好極了
- All right, Madame Blanche, you found me.  - Music to my ears.
我非常願意聽取你的要求
I'm perfectly willing to listen to your demands,
不論是什麼  但不是現在
whatever they might be, but not right now.
沒有要求  亞當森先生  噢  不  不  不
No demands, Mr. Adamson. Oh, no, no, no!
是幾乎沒有  朱莉亞·蘭伯特  不會向你要求什麼
Hardly that. Julia Rainbird wants nothing from you...
但是你必須做她的繼承人  繼承所有蘭伯特家的財富
but the privilege of making you heir to the entire Rainbird fortune.
所有的  動人的數百萬美元
The whole, lovely millions and millions of it.
如果她有提出任何要求  那就是要我找到你
Now if she made any demands at all, they were on me to find you.
透過通靈的手段  那是當然的
Through psychic means, of course.
讓我搞清楚一下
Let me get this straight.
這就是你和  你的朋友一直追查我的原因
Is that the only reason you and your friend have been, shall we say, investigating me?
喔  是的  不要以為這很容易
Oh, yes. And don't think it's been easy.
噢  亞當森先生  你給了我和喬治魔鬼般的考驗
Oh, Mr. Adamson, you've given George and me the devil's own time of it.
追蹤打從你嬰兒時期被遺棄開始
Tracing you from a foundling baby...
一直到叫做休奎奇的青年  然後是叫做亞當森的男士
to a young boy named Shoebridge to a man named Adamson.
噢  但是  亞當森先生  你就在這裡  我也在這裡
Oh, but, Mr. Adamson, here you are, : Here I am.
這對我們來說  真是快樂的時刻  不是嗎
It's a happy moment for us all, isn't it?
是主教
It's the Bishop.
有誰知道你來這裡
Does anyone know that you've come here?
沒有人知道
No one know...
有誰會知道
Anyone kn-know?
不  連靈魂也沒有
No. Not a soul.
即使是喬治的靈魂
Not even George soul.
你沒有什麼好擔心的  亞當森先生
You have nothing to worry about, Mr. Adamson.
我保證
I promise.
我不會吐露半個字  給任何人
I won't breathe a word... to anyone.
看來布蘭琪·泰勒女士  需要休息一下
It looks like Miss Tyler needs some rest.
你不聽我的話
Will you do as I say?
不  不
No. No.
打開門
Unlock the door.
高興一點  法蘭
Cheer up, Fran.
讓我們去取新的鑽石  來裝飾我們的吊燈吧
Let's go get the new diamond for our chandelier.
哇  真是漂亮
Wow. It's gorgeous.
現在輪到布蘭琪女士了
And now for Madame Blanche.
噢  我的天
Oh, my God.
布蘭琪
Blanche?
如果我說得太多  也許是因為你不說話
If I'm talking too much, perhaps it's because you're not talking.
我胃痛  亞瑟  它不同意謀殺
It's my stomach, Arthur. Murder doesn't agree with it.
你以為我很期待
You think I'm looking forward to it?
如果喬森·馬洛尼能幹一點  他們現在早就都死了
If Joe Maloney had been more efficient, they'd both be dead by now.
你可以拿走我的那一份  亞瑟
You can have my share, Arthur.
你可以把兩顆鑽石都佔為己有  只要你能結束一切
You can keep both diamonds all to yourself if you'll just end it.
我會告訴你該怎麼做
I'll tell you what I'll do.
如果你幫我把這個睡美人  從地窖搬到我們的車上
If you help me carry Sleeping Beauty up out of the cellar, load her into our car...
開車送她去荒蕪的公路  那些可以自殺的地方
and drive her out to some deserted road where a suicide can take place,
我向你保證  我們可以來討論這件事
I promise you we'll talk this thing over.
-好嗎  -計程車司機怎麼辦
- Okay?  - What about the cab driver?
如果她能找到我們  我相信他也可以
If she was able to find us, I'm sure he can too.
-他逃不出我們的手掌心  -是你的手  不是我的
- He'll walk right into our hands.  - Your hands, not mine.
你不覺得我們  應該下去看一看她嗎
Don't you think we ought to go down and take a look at her?
自從我們給她注射以來  已經有一段時間了
It's been a while since we gave her that shot.
-你去  -好吧
- You do it.  - Okay.
你會很高興知道她仍然昏迷著
You'll be happy to know she's still unconscious.
-布蘭琪  -噓
- Blanche.  - Shh!
我會這樣結束  把管子的一端
I'll put this end into her exhaust pipe...
接到排氣管  另一端放在車窗中
and the other end in the window.
這樣看來就像是自殺
That way, it'll look like suicide.
最好現在就去把她帶過來
Better go and get her now.
我要把她放在我們車裡  你開她的
I'll take her in our car. You follow in hers.
你抓住她的雙腳
You take hold of her feet.
老天  她還真重
Jesus, she's heavy.
喬治
George!
抓到他們了
Got 'em.
布蘭琪  你演的太好了
Blanche, you faked that one beautifully.
你仍然是冠軍
You are still the champ.
謝謝  喬治
Thank you, George.
你知道這兩個的賞金值多少嗎
Do you realize how much the reward is for those two?
是的
Yes.
但是你知道  如果我們能夠
But do you realize how much more the reward would be...
找到鑽石  還會有多少獎勵嗎
if we could find the diamonds and turn 'em in?
你怎麼了
What's the matter with you?
我
I...
布蘭琪  怎麼回事
Blanche, what's the matter?
怎麼了
What is it?
布蘭琪  你辦到了
Blanche, you did it!
你真是個通靈師
You are psychic!
-我們在樓梯上幹嘛  -你不再是假的
- What am I doing here on the stairs?  - You're not a fake.
你真的找到了一個  瞧
You actually found one. Look.
我找到的
I did?
我要打電話給警察  告訴他們好消息
I'll get the police on the phone and give them our good news,
還要通知蘭伯特女士  告訴她壞消息
and call Miss Rainbird and give her the bad.
接線生  能幫我接通警察局嗎
Operator, can I have the police?